viewscraze.com 2016-10-29

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for ViewsCraze.com

The privacy of our visitors to ViewsCraze.com is important to us.

At ViewsCraze.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit ViewsCraze.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, ViewsCraze.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
ViewsCraze.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on ViewsCraze.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to ViewsCraze.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ViewsCraze.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
ViewsCraze.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. ViewsCraze.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
